During your weekend here,
you will explore ways,
through yoga, breathing,
and other mindful practices,
to reconnect with yourself
and your partner.
Also, for a small donation,
we have an on-site shaman
who can heal your chakras.
Small donation?
Sounds like a "chakra con."
[cellphone chimes]Oh.
You're supposed
to turn that off.
I'm sorry.
It's work.
Okay,
so is a marriage.
You know, we traveled all this
way. The least you could do
is take this
seriously.
I'm sorry.
You're right.[cellphone chimes]
Oh, my God, that -- that
crappy breakfast was $55.
For flax
and berries.
Yeah.
I thought this was supposed to
be one fee up front, all in.
I wish youwere all in,
Mitchell.
I'm sor-- I am.
Starting...now.
Okay?
Okay.
[bell chimes]That wasn't me.
I have invited the Tibetan
Singing Bowl to ring,
reminding us to all
turn down the volume
and find the beauty
in silence.
[group cheering]
That was unfortunate.
My apologies. We happen to be
next door to the Royals.
[gasps] Oh, my God,
we just binged The Crown.
W-W-Which royals?
William and Kate?
Harry and
the Suitsgirl?
Actually, it's the Kansas City
Royals. Spring training,
their practice field
is next door.[gasps]
Growing up a Royals fan,
it was always my dream
to see them at
spring training.
So, I just decided,
after the retreat was over,
I'm just gonna swing by,
you know, grab an autograph,
maybe whisper an opinion
in the manager's ear,
be discovered as
a great baseball mind.
Then the Yankees
would come calling,
and I'd have to choose
between the team I love
and the -- the big payout.
But I'm getting ahead
of myself.
RANDY: Not to worry. This is
their last day of training,
and they leave tonight.
Excuse me,
question.
Yes.
Yes, hi. Will we have
an opportunity to explore
these -- these beautiful
grounds on our own?
Absolutely.
Tomorrow at sunset.
After goat yoga.
Oh, my God!
Can it get any worse?!
♪♪
Arrgh! Ughh!
What are you doing?
I grunted less
when I was giving birth
to Joe.
You were pushing six and a half
pounds, I'm pushing 220.
You're dressing younger.
You're exercising.
You only had one breakfast
this morning.
Who is she, Jay?
I'll kill her.
Relax, would you?
I'm just trying to get in shape.
Okay, but hurry,
because we have to go
and pick up Joe
at the birthday party.
Wait a minute.
Is that what this
is all about --
Henry's father?
I don't understand
why you're so insecure
just because
he's younger,
stronger, and more rugged
than you are.
Go easy. I'm working on
only one breakfast.
Joe won't shut up about
his new friend's dad.
"Henry's dad is so tough."
Who cares?
He was a stunt double in
a couple of Bournemovies.
From the first time
Joe went over there,
that guy's been trying
to prove how cool he is.
[tires screech]Joe! Let's go!
Heads up!
[engine revs]
What the hell?!
-Yeah!
He's Jason Bourne!
That's make-believe.
Matt Damon's Jason Bourne.
Growing up, I thought
my dad was the coolest.
And that made me feel
good about myself.
I mean,
I try to stay with it.
Exactly! Look at you,
you even have a smart watch.
Yeah, the damn thing tells me
when to stand up,
when to breathe.[watch beeps]
Your body mass
index is --
Nobody asked!
Which have more chromosomes,
potatoes or humans?
Humans, right?
Potatoes?!
[laughs]
Oh, Krazy Kups,
what can't you teach us?
Are you doing all this to
impress Haley's boyfriend?
Haley's dating this genius
astrophysics professor
who's somehow
making her smarter
because, last week,
I called Pluto a planet
and Haley
laughed at me.
In pity.
Haley.
Do we think that Haley
is suited to a professor,
because I more saw her
with a Gilligan type?
Come on, now.
Lots of happy couples
aren't the exact same
level of smart.
That's true.
We work.
Yeah.
Wait.
When you say, "We work,"
do you think you're smarter
than me or I'm smarter than you?
I think I'm smart enough
not to have this conversation.
Oh, my God!
You do! You think
you're smarter than me!
Okay, hotshot.
How many patents do you have?
Headscratcher TM,
Aspirin Gun,
Polite Car Horn that'll
put an end to road rage.
[high-pitched] Excuse me,
excuse me, excuse me.
Can we just not get into a whole
thing before this lunch?
What lunch?
I just ate a pie.
Your sister is dating
a professor of astrophysics,
and he's coming here
today to meet us.
Oh, good,
someone to talk to.
I'm tired of dumbing it down
for you chuckle-heads.
Bill, are you on your way?
Stay in the car.
I'll meet you outside.
It was hard for me when Haley
started dating Arvin,
my professor
and science hero and...
okay, fine, crush.
I was so upset, I went home,
and I may have overindulged...
on Bagel Bites.[microwave beeps]
[smoke alarm ringing]
Hey.
-Aah!
-It's okay. You're safe.
But I'm gonna need you
to come with me.
I don't really
think you need --
Okay.
He was like a superhero.
Is that your dad?
A beautiful...
not-so-smart superhero.
The last thing I wanted
was Professor Fennerman
finding out
I was dating a dummy.
A sweet, chiseled dummy.
Alex, you didn't mention you've
got a firefighter boyfriend.
Yeah! It's great.
"Take that, you fire."
We gotta go.
Oh, but your parents just
invited me to stay for lunch.
Score!
By the way, you look way younger
than your poster.
We really should
get going before we --
we miss our -- our plans
and stuff, right?
Oh.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah...
Alex! I didn't know you were
joining us for lunch.
Oh! No, no.
My -- My friend and I
have some plans
we really
can't get out of.
Oh, no, I could totally just
show you Backdraftlater.
It's my brother's DVD.
He doesn't even know I took it.
So...
Mom, Dad,
this is Arvin.
Hello, Arvin.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Yes, you are the first
TED Talkin' science superstar
we've ever had
in our house.
Mm-hmm.
Well, as long as I'm a
"superstar" and not a supernova.
[laughter]
You don't even know what
you're laughing at.
I get it.I got it more.
I don't get it, but, uh, you
sound like Austin Powers, man.
Wow. Henry's dad
did such a great job
with the birthday party
for the kids, huh?
"Henry's dad."
I took Joe
to see African Queen
in CinemaScope.
Oh, hey.
Good to see you again, Jay.
GLORIA: Hi.Hi, I'm Clay.
I'd shake your hand,
but I'm a little banged up.
I feel out of a five-story
building this morning,
into a net.
He fell out of bed
this morning.
Ah. Hey, honey.
Come down and meet
these guys.
-Oh, hey!
-[chuckling] Wow.
Welcome.
I'm Jenny, Henry's mom.
Joe's parents --
Jay, Gloria.
Hi.
Gloria.
Mama! Henry's mom just did
the wall so fast!
You try it.
Oh, I climb already into
these heels this morning.
It's too much
for me today.
I'm going up again!
Okay.
Oh, I used to love
wearing shoes like that.
But after marching around in
combat boots for two years,
I made a deal with my feet
I would never hurt them again.
[laughter]My beautiful wife
did two tours in Iraq.
Oh.Wow, Gloria, you're not
that different.
Yesterday, she did
two tours of a sales rack.
[laughs]
Help! I'm too high!
Oh.
Go ahead, just jump,
buddy. I'll catch ya.
But your sciatica!
I'm on it.
What is the hurry?
He's on a rope.
She's making quite
a meal out of this.Yeah.
[cheers and applause]
Attaboy.
Thank you, Jenny.
You're so cool.
Ah, look at that, Gloria.
She saved him.
Just like she
saved America.
Can I have some more cake?
Jenny made it.
I used to cook
for my squadron.
You've done so
many great things
that you keep
telling us about.
[laughs]
Here we are --
our sensory deprivation tanks
will disconnect you
from the world
and connect you
with yourselves.
Okay, so, this looks
a little coffin-y.
So, I'm not so sure.
About my husband.
He had an MRI last year,
and he sort of freaked out.
So, do you have
anything bigger,
like, an indoor pool
or a -- a family tank?
Okay, Mitchell,
I'm -- I'm fine.
We're here to evolve
and grow...
Well...
So, the float lasts
for one hour,
during which most people
simply experience
a deep, relaxed state.
Most people?
What -- What about the rest?
What -- What do
they experience?
Okay, a-are these scratches
on this lid here?Oh, come on, Mitchell.
The flower that blooms
in adversity
is the most rare
and beautiful of all.
Very well put.
He didn't make that up.
It's from Mulan.
Our daughter made us
watch it a thousand times.
Well, I --
Well, I'm lashing!
[laughs] Okay,
maybe we should just float.
Yeah,
let's just float.Yeah, okay.
Okay.
[water trickling]
[exhales shakily]
I tried to relax in there,
I really did.
But it was difficult.
I-I guess because I felt
like I was, um --
Oh, what's the word?
Dying.
But I got past that,
only to start reliving every
mistake I have ever made,
like when I went to
an Oscar party and I said
"Bett" Davis in front of a room
full of vicious gays.
Honestly, the only thing
that kept me in there
was the knowledge that Cam
was right next door.
Go Royals! I-I love you!
It was a solid plan --
just go for a quick peek,
take some pictures,
run back, splash some water
in my hair,
"Oh, Mitchell, isn't floating
so relaxing?"
[indistinct shouting]
[bat clangs]
Got it!
Nice catch.
Oh.
That was good.
Oh, my gosh. Uh, M-Mr. Brett.
I didn't know you would be here.
Hi. Call me George.Oh, George.
Yeah, how are ya?Uh, good.
My name's Cameron.
Nice to meet you, Cam.
Nice to meet you.
Been a fan for --
Hey, do you mind if
I get a picture?
Not at all. Not at all.
300 bucks,
how's that sound?
I'm retired.
300?I'm just kidding.
Oh.
[both laugh]
Come on, it's free.
Okay -- Ow!
[both laugh]
Alright.[cellphone camera clicks]
There it is.
There they are! Oh, my God!There ya go! There ya go!
Well, listen, I don't want to
take up too much of your time.
Thank you s--
I got all the time
in the world.
I'm not playing.
I'm just coaching.
Ohh.
Okay.
Yeah. Come here.
Let me tell you the story
about the Pine Tar game.
Oh, wow!
You wanna
hear that?
Sure.
Come on.
Okay.
But first, let me
tell you about --
I'm gonna tell you about dinner
the night before.
Oh.
You must be
the genius boyfriend.
That is what
the guys call me.
They're always,
like, you know,
"Hey, genius."
I'm like, "Hey, guys."
So, tell me,
are there aliens?
You kidding? 100%.
Oh, I knew it. Wait,
and the zombiepocalypse?
Dude, I tell everyone,
"Start building up an immunity
to zombie bites. Now."
I'm so glad we talked.
Um. Sorry for
the interruption.
Everything okay?
Well, the short story
is, yes.
The -- The long story is,
the theory
on which I've based
much of my career
has just been disproven.
What? Your Vacuum
Energy Density Theory?
I'm -- I'm so sorry.
Me, too.
That was the density theory
I thought really worked.
Really, Phil, what
was your second choice?
Well, that's all part
of the process, isn't it?
My theory actually invalidated
someone else's.
Mm.
He jumped off a building --
just very dramatic.
But, well, I'm British.
So, no worries.
[sighs]
What smells so good?Uh. Uh, it's the chicken!
So, Bill,
you are a firefighter?
Yeah, my three favorite things
are helping people,
sliding down poles,
and hanging off trucks,
so I figured might as well
make a career out of it.
Well, it's good that
your favorite things
weren't chloroform, duct tape,
and windowless vans.
[laughter]
Claire, the joke is
he'd be a kidnapper.
I got it.
You know, Phil used to think
it was "duck" tape.
[laughs]
Like, duck.
Claire didn't understand
the ending of La La Land.
Sorry. They're not
normally like this.
Clearly, they're
going through something
they can't even drop
for one important lunch.
They're arguing over
who's smarter,
and there's only one way
to settle it.
Another time, in the presence
of a marriage counselor?
Nope. Brain Battle.
No. No, we're not doing
that right now.
I'm so sorry, Arvin.
We're being silly.
"How many presidents
died in office?"
-Eight.
-Six.
The correct answer
is eight.
Ha! Ha!
Damn it.
Give me another one.
Why was six afraid of seven?
'Cause seven, eight, nine.
[chuckles]
You know,
like he "ate" it.
"Who wrote Moby-Dick?"
Herman Munster.
HermanMunster.
Herman Melville.Melville!
"How many moons
does Jupiter have?"
Oh, is it alright
if I take this one?Mm-hmm.
27.
67.
Hmm? No, that's --
that's wrong.
67 is Uranus and Jupiter's 27,
right, Alex?
Actually, no.
But it's
a simple mistake, though.
You just flipped them.
Well, this is mortifying,
isn't it?
I have a doctorate
in astrophysics. Idiot.
First, some puffed-up Swedes
invalidate my life's work.
And then I'm bested by
a little bedtime gurgle cup!
I'm sorry.
I'm going to need a moment.
67 moons.
What an idiot.
[footsteps]
Well, all's I know is
the Earth only has one moon
and I saw a documentary
and, uh, we didn't even
land on it.
Oh, my God,
stop talking.
You know,
you're being kind of mean.
I'm gonna need
a moment, too.
This is why I don't bring
boyfriends home.
Why didn't you ask me before
inviting him to lunch?
"This Paul Newman character
had a 'cool hand'?"
Luke!
Yep.
Counts! Counts.
Henry's dad climbed the wall
with one hand! It was awesome!
Yeah, well, his career
rides on Matt Damon
not doing any artsy,
think-y movies,
so I wouldn't
count on Henry
going to your school
much longer.[siren chirps]
[tires screech, siren wailing]
What the hell?
I made that light.
Oh, geez.
Another ticket.
Henry's mom drove a tank!
Henry's mom!
[engine revs]What are you doing,
Gloria?
I want to see
Henry's mom do this!
[tires screech]
[siren wailing]
Yay! He's chasing us!
This feels like
a bad idea.
Okay, too late, because
I'm already committed!
[watch beeps]
Heart rate -- high.
Heart rate -- high.What is the plan,
Gloria?
We're going to the mall!
You know I tease you
about your shopping,
but you do
have a problem.
[tires screech]
Okay. Get down
and don't move.
That's gonna be tough.
I can smell Cinnabon.
Hey!
Where have you been?
Oh, hey.
I just stayed in the tank
a little -- a little extra.
How -- What a great
experience.
Just being alone
with yourself -- Oh!
Oh, I was never alone.
I-I saw the face
of every bully,
I replayed every
humiliation --
Okay. Is this about
"Bett" Davis again?
Okay, we had just watched
Ruthless People.
You're thinking Midler.
You gotta let it go.
I know.
I'm -- I'm gonna try.
But as scared
as I was in there,
I kept thinking
about how
you're the one person
who makes me feel safe.
And it -- it made me want to be
a better husband...
Aww.
...to be more present,
to be more understanding,
to --
Why's --
Why's your face red?Oh, is it?
Yeah.
Is it?
Oh, just probably 'cause
of the toxins, you know --
And your arms, too,
but only up to the --
You have a farmer's tan.
What have I told you
about that expression?
I can say it, but --
Oh, my --
T-That's why you're burned.
You went Royal watching!
I was only gonna stay for
a second, but George Brett --
George -- George Brett
cornered me.
Who?
And you know how I am
with famous people.
I can't say "No."
Remember when I spent
the entire day at the pool
with Downtown Julie Brown?
You shamed me
into coming here
only to leave me soaking in a --
in a bowl of trauma soup?
Okay, whoa, whoa.
W-What happened about be--
being more understanding?
I-I can't believe you're turning
this into my fault.
This is so like you, Cam.
This --
Hello, again.
Please follow me to
your guided silent meditation.
Before we begin,
the chef has asked me
to reassure everyone
that there's nothing wrong
with the tempeh.
It's supposed to
taste that way.
Alright.
Deep breath.
In through the nose.
Out through the mouth.
Only in silence can we
be truly present.
But be prepared --
errant feelings may arise.
Anxiety, doubt, anger...
Now, take a breath
and let those feelings pass
like clouds in the sky.
The tension is melting away.
That's it.
Live in this moment of serenity
and stillness.
We're so accustomed to
going, going, going.
But we need to just stop.
Ask yourself
the important questions.
Are you running away
from difficult feelings?
[no audio]
Are you holding on
to petty grievances?
Are you being the best you?
It's not too late
to find your way back.
To the light,
to forgiveness,
to love.
It was amazing.
There were no words,
but I could feel Cam
taking full responsibility
for our fight.
Total silence,
but Mitchell's eyes said,
"It's all on me."
You know, "I was wrong.
What would I do without you?"
It was a beautiful weekend.
Plus, George Brett
signed my ball.
[chuckles]
Oh, "To Cam, all my best wishes,
George Brett.
P.S. We are not done with this"?
Mitchell!
Did you write on my ball?!
Hey, where's Bill?
I don't know.
He's probably outside.
When he gets agitated,
he likes to climb stuff.
That lunch was insane.
Can you believe Mom and Dad?
No, and, uh,
I can't believe you, either.
You're so mean to Bill.
What do you have
against hot people?
What did we ever
do to you?
You lost me.
You're gonna blow it
with that guy,
and he's really nice.
Why do you have to
make him feel so dumb?
Okay, you don't know
what you're talking about.
Oh, yes, I do.
Because it's the same way
you've always treated me.
It sucks.
You know what Arvin
never does?
Makes me feel
less smart than him.
So, who cares if Bill's
not a member of Menses?
Look, this is the first
boyfriend you've ever had
that is age appropriate,
employed,
and doesn't look like
he's dying on a ship.
I wouldn't say
"boyfriend."
He's more like
a guilty pleasure.
Guilty or not, that's the first
time I've ever heard you
describe a guy
as a "pleasure."
Bill, I'm sorry!
BILL: All good, babe.
You're the one fire
I can't put out.
Well, also grease
is pretty tricky.
Arvin?
TOGETHER: Oh.
Arvin, hi.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Oh, yes. Yes.
Um...yes.
I-I'm -- I'm just
a-a little embarrassed.
We're the ones who should
be embarrassed.
We just made lunch
so tense and weird.
Yeah.
Well, I'm --
I'm not terribly adept
at handling failure.
My parents are both
overachieving academics --
a doctor of philosophy and a --
a doctor of mathematics.
Oh.
Wow!
And Father is
a doctor of medicine
and a doctor of economics.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
I-I just need to shake it off.
You know,
stiff-upper-lip it.
[chuckles]
Yeah, it's fine.
Can we just pretend
it never happened?
No.
No, failure sucks.
It's okay to feel bad.
Yeah, wallow a little.
Eat some ice cream.
Day drink, that's how you
come out the other side.
[clicks tongue]
You're -- You're like
the inverse of my parents.
Except the drinking.
They're pickled
most of the day.
Well, you're not
in their house.
This is House Dunphy --
We fail here.
Right. I mean,
today our whole goal
was to impress you.
We made fools of ourselves.
I have a magic shop that's
bleeding money -- thousands.
What?
It's fine.
Hey, what's all this, then?
Oh, whoa.
Did I get that from you?
Am I becoming Madonna?
Your parents were actually
being quite lovely.
Thank you for
taking the time.
Oh, and my parents' walls
may be adorned
with nothing
but degrees and awards,
but they don't have one tenth
of your emotional intelligence.
Aww!
Thank you.
But would you say it's an
absolutely equal emotional...If you had to
pick a winner --
Okay, stop it....intelligence.
Just --
[footsteps]
That was so fun.
My heart is racing.
You? My watch dialed
my cardiologist.
I've never run
from the cops before.
Me either.[siren chirps]
Lights!
I can't wait to tell everyone
how cool you guys are!
We're not cool, Joe.
That's not
what people do
when a policeman
pulls them over.
In fact, there's nothing
cool about us.
Well, I don't think
we should be lumped into --
[siren chirps]Lights!
Joe, there are more important
things than being cool.
Uh, like what?
Look, the point is, Joe,
we love you too much
to let you think dumb moves
like this are okay.
So, what do we do now?
We're gonna do
the right thing.
[seat belt clicks]
[vehicle door closes]
Officer!
Uh...
Where's Cinnabon?
GEORGE:
Sure enough, they call me out
for using too much pine tar.
I run out there and just go
berserk on these umpires.
But everybody
remembers --Ugh!
Watch out.
That's a base.Yeah. Yeah.
That's third base.Third base.
That's where I used to play.
You remember that?
Yeah. Yeah.
Should we do --
So, when you would
stand here,
you would just kind of basically
be in an athletic --
I played college
football --You would get here.
GEORGE: You would get
right here like this and say,
"Please don't
hit it to me."
[both laugh]
CAM:
That's how I feel!
I'm gonna get you back!
[laughs]
--Captions by VITAC--